Hirsh Health Sciences Library Records UA225
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Slide library, 1893 -- 1998; UA225.004; 1.2 Linear Feet; 937 Digital Object(s)
  - Departments and Divisions, Research, Programs, Finances, Fund Raising and Governance, 1950 -- 1993; UA225.004.001.00004; Tufts University School of Medicine
    - Posner Hall, West Wing for orthopedic patients and staff, Dr. Harris's Office, 3rd Floor, UA225.004.001.00004.00118; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Boston (Mass.); Buildings; Slides (photographs); Harris, John; Posner Hall; Boston Campus
    - Posner Hall, West Wing for orthopedic patients and staff, Dr. Goldberg's Office, 3rd Floor, UA225.004.001.00004.00119; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Boston (Mass.); Buildings; Slides (photographs); Goldberg, Michael J.; Posner Hall; Boston Campus
    - Posner Hall, West Wing for orthopedic patients and staff, Dr. Donaldson's Office (Regina) 3rd Floor, UA225.004.001.00004.00120; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo, woman in office
      Boston (Mass.); Buildings; Slides (photographs); Donaldson, William R.; Posner Hall; Boston Campus
    - Posner Hall, West Wing for orthopedic patients and staff, Dr. Scheller's Office, 3rd Floor, UA225.004.001.00004.00121; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Boston (Mass.); Buildings; Slides (photographs); Scheller, Arnold; Posner Hall; Boston Campus
    - Posner Hall, West Wing for orthopedic patients and staff, Dr. Belkin's Office, 4th Floor, UA225.004.001.00004.00122; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Boston (Mass.); Buildings; Slides (photographs); Belkin, Stuart C.; Posner Hall; Boston Campus
    - Posner Hall, West Wing for orthopedic patients and staff, Dr. Banks's Office, 4th Floor, UA225.004.001.00004.00123; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Boston (Mass.); Buildings; Slides (photographs); Banks, Henry H. (1921-); Posner Hall; Boston Campus
    - Posner Hall, West Wing for orthopedic patients and staff, Library, 4th Floor, UA225.004.001.00004.00124; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo, conference room
    - Posner Hall, West Wing for orthopedic patients and staff, Bookkeeping, 4th Floor, UA225.004.001.00004.00125; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Dr. Child's quote #1, UA225.004.001.00004.00126; Tufts University (Box 1)
      1 February 1956
      Quotation; Specialties, Surgical; Education; Slides (photographs); Child, Charles G., III
    - Dr. Child's quote #2, UA225.004.001.00004.00127; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Quotation; Internship and residency; Education; Slides (photographs); Child, Charles G., III
    - NIH Appropriations, 1950 -- 1989; UA225.004.001.00004.00128; Tufts University (Box 1)
      National Institute of Health Appropriations 1950-1989
      1950; 1951; 1952; 1953; 1954; 1955; 1956; 1957; 1958; 1959; 1960; 1961; 1962; 1963; 1964; 1965; 1966; 1967; 1968; 1969; 1970; 1971; 1972; 1973; 1974; 1975; 1976; 1977; 1978; 1979; 1980; 1981; 1982; 1983; 1984; 1985; 1986; 1987; 1988; 1989; Slides (photographs)
    - TUSM Research Activity, 1983 -- 1984; UA225.004.001.00004.00129; Tufts University (Box 1)
      TUSM Research Activity
      National Institutes of Health (U.S.)--Appropriations and expenditures.; Slides (photographs)
    - Sponsored research programs, 1969 -- 1985; UA225.004.001.00004.00130; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Sponsored Programs 1969-1970, 1984-1985
      1969; 1970; 1984; 1985; Research; Slides (photographs)
    - TUSM Research Activity, 1984 -- 1985; UA225.004.001.00004.00131; Tufts University (Box 1)
      1984; 1958; Research; Slides (photographs)
    - TUSM research award level, 1984 -- 1985; UA225.004.001.00004.00132; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Sponsored Research-Health Sciences
      1984-1985; Research; Slides (photographs)
    - TUSM research activity, 1986; UA225.004.001.00004.00133; Tufts University (Box 1)
      1986; Research; Slides (photographs)
    - TUSM research activity, 1987; UA225.004.001.00004.00134; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Sponsored Research Support for School of Medicine Faculty
      1987; Research; Slides (photographs)
    - TUSM research and education projects, 1985 -- 1988; UA225.004.001.00004.00135; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Medical School Research and Educational Projects
      1985; 1986; 1987; 1988; Research; Slides (photographs)
    - TUSM research activity, 1988; UA225.004.001.00004.00136; Tufts University (Box 1)
      1988; Research; Slides (photographs)
    - TUSM research dollars, 1981 -- 1988; UA225.004.001.00004.00137; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Medical School Research Trend of ICR and Direct
      1981; 1982; 1983; 1984; 1985; 1986; 1987; 1988; 1989; Research; Slides (photographs)
    - TUSM research grants and contracts, 1980 -- 1989; UA225.004.001.00004.00138; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Medical Faculty Grants and Contracts
      1980; 1981; 1982; 1983; 1984; 1985; 1986; 1987; 1988; 1989; Research; Slides (photographs)
    - TUSM research grants and contracts, 1980 -- 1989; UA225.004.001.00004.00139; Tufts University (Box 1)
      1980; 1981; 1982; 1983; 1984; 1985; 1986; 1987; 1988; 1990; Research; Slides (photographs)
    - TUSM research grants agrant success rate, 1987 -- 1989; UA225.004.001.00004.00140; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Research Grant Success Rate
      1987; 1988; 1989; Research; Slides (photographs)
    - TUSM research activity, 1988 -- 1989; UA225.004.001.00004.00141; Tufts University (Box 1)
      TUSM Research Activity 1989-1990
      1989; 1990; Research; Slides (photographs)
    - TUSM sponsored programs, 1969 -- 1990; UA225.004.001.00004.00142; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Sponsored Programs 1969-1970, 1989-1990
      1969; 1970; 1989; 1990; Research; Slides (photographs)
    - TUSM research activity, 1991 -- 1992; UA225.004.001.00004.00143; Tufts University (Box 1)
      TUSM Research Activit 1991-1992|NEMCH and TNEMC, Boston VAMC, St. Elizabeths, Bay State Medical Center
      1991; 1992; Research; Slides (photographs)
    - TUSM research activity, 1993; UA225.004.001.00004.00144; Tufts University (Box 1)
      TUSM Grant and Contract Activity 1993
      1993; Research; Slides (photographs)
    - TUSM research space, 1983 -- 1990; UA225.004.001.00004.00145; Tufts University (Box 1)
      TUSM Research Space
      1983; 1990; Research; Slides (photographs)
    - TUSM needed research space, 1988 -- 1991; UA225.004.001.00004.00146; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Needed Medical School Research and Education Projects 1988-1991
      1988; 1989; 1990; 1991; Research; Slides (photographs)
    - Programs: International Affiliations, UA225.004.001.00004.00147; Tufts University (Box 1)
      International Affiliations: Africa, Europe, Far East, Middle East, South America
      Medical colleges; Slides (photographs)
    - Signing affiliation protocol with Guangzhou Medical College, 1984-11-13; UA225.004.001.00004.00148; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo: 5 people at meeting
      China.; Medical colleges; Slides (photographs)
    - Signing affiliation protocol with Guangzhou Medical College, 1984-11-13; UA225.004.001.00004.00149; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo: 9 people at meeting signing documents
    - Signing affiliation protocol with Guangzhou Medical College, 1984-11-13; UA225.004.001.00004.00150; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo: 5 people at meeting, toasting
    - Finances, UA225.004.001.00004.00151; Tufts University (Box 1)
      "Finances"
      Financial Support; Medical colleges; Slides (photographs)
    - Sources of revenue for United States medical schools, 1960 -- 1982; UA225.004.001.00004.00152; Tufts University (Box 1)
      AAMC Distrubution of sources of revenue for medical schools 1960-61 through 1981-82
    - Financial support United States medical schools, UA225.004.001.00004.00153; Tufts University (Box 1)
      AAMC Financial support of U.S. Medical School 1960-61 through 1981-82
    - Financial support United States medical schools, UA225.004.001.00004.00154; Tufts University (Box 1)
      U.S. medical schools Sources of financial support
    - Federal, state, and other funds to public and private schools, 1971 -- 1983; UA225.004.001.00004.00155; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Federal, State, and other funds to public and private schools
    - Revenue comparison between TUSM and other medical schools, UA225.004.001.00004.00156; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Comparison Between TUSM and Other U.S. Medical Schools
    - TUSM budget sources and use of funds, 1984; UA225.004.001.00004.00157; Tufts University (Box 1)
      TUSM Budget 1983-84: Sources and uses of funds
      Budget; FY1983; Slides (photographs)
    - TUSM budget, 1984 -- 1985; UA225.004.001.00004.00158; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Budget; FY1984; Slides (photographs)
    - TUSM net budget, 1984 -- 1985; UA225.004.001.00004.00159; Tufts University (Box 1)
      FY 1985-1986 Budget
      Budget; FY1985; Slides (photographs)
    - TUSM budget, 1985 -- 1986; UA225.004.001.00004.00160; Tufts University (Box 1)
      TUSM Budget 1984-85: Sources and uses of funds
      Budget; Slides (photographs)
    - TUSM budget, 1986 -- 1987; UA225.004.001.00004.00161; Tufts University (Box 1)
      TUSM Budget 1986-87: Sources and uses of funds
    - TUSM net budget, UA225.004.001.00004.00162; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - TUSM revenue composition, 1986 -- 1987; UA225.004.001.00004.00163; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Revenue Composition between Northeast Private Schools and TUSM
    - Impact of Tupper move, UA225.004.001.00004.00164; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Impact of Tupper move
      Buildings; Slides (photographs)
    - TUSM budget, 1987 -- 1988; UA225.004.001.00004.00165; Tufts University (Box 1)
      TUSM Budget 1987-88: Sources and uses of funds
    - TUSM budget, 1988 -- 1989; UA225.004.001.00004.00166; Tufts University (Box 1)
      1988-89
    - TMCA support of TUSM, UA225.004.001.00004.00167; Tufts University (Box 1)
      FY1976-1987 Support Funds
    - TMCA support of TUSM, UA225.004.001.00004.00168; Tufts University (Box 1)
      FY1977-86, FY1987, FY1988, FY1989, FY1990
    - TUSM budget, 1989; UA225.004.001.00004.00169; Tufts University (Box 1)
      FY1989
    - Built in expenses, 1990; UA225.004.001.00004.00170; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Medical School FY1990 Built-in Expenses
    - TUSM budget, 1990; UA225.004.001.00004.00171; Tufts University (Box 1)
      FY1990 Budget income and expense
    - TUSM budget income, 1990; UA225.004.001.00004.00172; Tufts University (Box 1)
      FY1990 Net Budget Income
    - TUSM net expense budget, 1990; UA225.004.001.00004.00173; Tufts University (Box 1)
      FY1990 Net Expense Budget
    - Sources of revenue, TUSM and New England private schools, UA225.004.001.00004.00174; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Tufts versus N.E. Private Schools Sources of Income
    - TUSM total budget, 1991; UA225.004.001.00004.00175; Tufts University (Box 1)
      FY1991 Total Budget Income and Expense
    - TUSM net budget, 1991; UA225.004.001.00004.00176; Tufts University (Box 1)
      FY1991 Net Budget Income and Expense
    - Actual income, 1991; UA225.004.001.00004.00177; Tufts University (Box 1)
      FY1991 Actual Income
    - Fiscal results, 1991; UA225.004.001.00004.00178; Tufts University (Box 1)
      FY1991 Results
      Endowments; Slides (photographs)
    - Endowment growth, 1980 -- 1988; UA225.004.001.00004.00179; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Endowment Growth
    - TUSM endowment, 1988; UA225.004.001.00004.00180; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Endowment 1988 for University and medical schools
    - TUSM endowment, 1990; UA225.004.001.00004.00181; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Endowment 1990 for University and medical schools
    - TUSM endowment, 1991; UA225.004.001.00004.00182; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Endowment 1991 for University and medical schools
    - Tufts endowment earnings, 1981 -- 1991; UA225.004.001.00004.00183; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Unrestricted Endowment Earnings 1981-1991
      FY1981; FY1982; FY1983; FY1984; FY1985; FY1986; FY1987; FY1988; FY1989; FY1990; FY1991; Endowments; Slides (photographs)
    - TUSM endowed chairs, 1988 -- 1990; UA225.004.001.00004.00184; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Endowed Chairs 1980, 1988, 1990
    - Annual Fund celebration with Dean Hayman, 1959; UA225.004.001.00004.00185; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo M1959, Class officers (G. F. Lord, H. L. Medlinksy, R. F. Cooney) present check to Dean Hayman
    - Class of 1960 with Dean Hayman, UA225.004.001.00004.00186; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo with five people
      M1960; Alumni and alumnae; Deans (Education); Slides (photographs); Hayman, Joseph M.
    - case statement, 1987; UA225.004.001.00004.00187; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo of man doing research
    - case statement, 1987; UA225.004.001.00004.00188; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo of two people doing research
    - case statement, 1987; UA225.004.001.00004.00189; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo of three people doing labwork
    - case statement, 1987; UA225.004.001.00004.00190; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Photo of two people in lab
    - Unrestricted annual fund, 1985 -- 1987; UA225.004.001.00004.00191; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Unrestricted Annual Fund FY1985-1987
    - Total annual fund, 1987; UA225.004.001.00004.00192; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Total Annual Fund FY1987
    - New Campaign, 1987; UA225.004.001.00004.00193; Tufts University (Box 1)
      The New Campaign
    - Annual fund, 1963 -- 1990; UA225.004.001.00004.00194; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Annual Fund FY1963, FY1986-1990
      FY1963; FY1986; FY1987; FY1988; FY1989; FY1990; Financial Support; Medical colleges; Slides (photographs)
    - M Club, 1986 -- 1990; UA225.004.001.00004.00195; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Millenium club: number of donors and total dollars, FY1986-1990
      FY1986; FY1987; FY1988; FY1989; FY1990; Endowments; Slides (photographs)
    - Capital achievement, 1985 -- 1990; UA225.004.001.00004.00196; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Campaign Achievement 1985-1990
      Endowments; Medical colleges; Slides (photographs)
    - Status of "New Campaign", 1990; UA225.004.001.00004.00197; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Capital Achievement, 1985 -- 1990; UA225.004.001.00004.00198; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Campaign Achievement 1985-1992
    - TUSM student phonathon, 1990; UA225.004.001.00004.00199; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Two people at table, working and answering phone calls
      Financial Support; Medical students; Slides (photographs)
    - TUSM student phonathon, 1990; UA225.004.001.00004.00200; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Person at table, working and answering calls
    - TUSM student phonathon, 1990; UA225.004.001.00004.00201; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Two people at table, working
    - TUSM student phonathon, 1990; UA225.004.001.00004.00202; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - TUSM student phonathon, 1990; UA225.004.001.00004.00203; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - TUSM student phonathon, 1990; UA225.004.001.00004.00204; Tufts University (Box 1)
  - Clinical Hospital Facilities, 1893 -- 1993; UA225.004.001.00005; Tufts University School of Medicine
    - Clinical teaching facilities, UA225.004.001.00005.00001; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Tufts hospitals, 1934; UA225.004.001.00005.00002; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Hospitals 1934, includes: Boston City, State Hospitals, Boston Dispensary, Beth Israel, Cambridge City, Providence Lying-In, Evangeline Booth, Worcester City, New England, Carney, Chapin, Quincy City, Maine General, Lynn, Malden
      Boston (Mass.); Teaching Hospitals; Slides (photographs); Boston City Hospital
    - Tufts hospitals, 1954 -- 1955; UA225.004.001.00005.00003; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Hospitals 1954-1955, includes: Boston City, Beth Israel, New England Medical Center, Boston V. A., St. Elizabeth's,, Boston State, Cambridge City, Carney, Chapin, Haynes, Malden, Providence L. I., St. Margaret's, Waltham
      Boston (Mass.); Teaching Hospitals; FY1955; Slides (photographs)
    - Tufts hospitals, 1959; UA225.004.001.00005.00004; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Medical education--Statistics|Tuition|Enrollment
      Boston (Mass.); Teaching Hospitals; 1959; Slides (photographs)
    - Tufts core teaching hospitals, 1985; UA225.004.001.00005.00005; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Boston (Mass.); Teaching Hospitals; Slides (photographs); Baystate Medical Center
    - Baystate Medical Center--Springfield Hospital, UA225.004.001.00005.00006; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Springfield (Mass.); Teaching Hospitals; Buildings; Parking lots; Automobiles; Slides (photographs); Baystate Medical Center
    - Baystate Medical Center Centennial Presentation, UA225.004.001.00005.00007; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Springfield (Mass.); 1883; 1893; Teaching Hospitals; Slides (photographs); Baystate Medical Center
    - Baystate Medical Center Centennial Presentation, advantages, UA225.004.001.00005.00008; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Baystate Medical Center Centennial Presentation, changes at TUSM, UA225.004.001.00005.00009; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Springfield (Mass.); Teaching Hospitals; Enrollment; Statistics; Curriculum; FY1955; FY1983; Slides (photographs); Baystate Medical Center
    - Baystate Medical Center Centennial Presentation, Tufts Teaching Hospitals, 1983; UA225.004.001.00005.00010; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Springfield (Mass.); Teaching Hospitals; Slides (photographs); Baystate Medical Center
    - Baystate Medical Center Centennial Presentation, students faculty research, UA225.004.001.00005.00011; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Baystate Medical Center Centennial Presentation, curriculum needs, UA225.004.001.00005.00012; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Springfield (Mass.); Curriculum; Slides (photographs); Baystate Medical Center
    - Baystate Medical Center Centennial Presentation, disadvantages, UA225.004.001.00005.00013; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Boston City Hospital, UA225.004.001.00005.00014; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Boston (Mass.); Buildings; Teaching Hospitals; Slides (photographs); Boston City Hospital
    - Boston City Hospital, UA225.004.001.00005.00015; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Boston City Hospital, UA225.004.001.00005.00016; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Boston City Hospital, UA225.004.001.00005.00017; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Boston City Hospital, pediatric patient, UA225.004.001.00005.00018; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Boston (Mass.); Orthopedics; Pediatrics; Nurses; Patients; Slides (photographs); Boston City Hospital
    - Beth Israel Hospital, 1929; UA225.004.001.00005.00019; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Boston (Mass.); Buildings; Teaching Hospitals; Slides (photographs); Beth Israel Hospital (Boston MA)
    - Boston City Hospital, UA225.004.001.00005.00020; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Old Emergency Ward in which the Shortell Unit for fractures was housed.
      Boston (Mass.); Buildings; Parking lots; Research; Emergency Service, Hospital; Orthopedics; Slides (photographs); Boston City Hospital; Shortell Unit
    - Boston City Hospital, 1965; UA225.004.001.00005.00021; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Boston City Hospital, Administration Building, UA225.004.001.00005.00022; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Boston City Hospital, Dowling Building & Amphitheater, UA225.004.001.00005.00023; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Boston (Mass.); Buildings; Teaching Hospitals; Auditoriums; Slides (photographs); Boston City Hospital
    - Boston City Hospital, Emergency entrance, UA225.004.001.00005.00024; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Boston (Mass.); Buildings; Teaching Hospitals; Ambulances; Slides (photographs); Boston City Hospital
    - Boston City Hospital, Tufts Research Unit, FGH Building, 1957; UA225.004.001.00005.00025; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Boston (Mass.); Buildings; Teaching Hospitals; Research; Slides (photographs); Boston City Hospital
    - Boston City Hospital including Tufts medical and research building, Tufts Research Unit, 1963; UA225.004.001.00005.00026; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Boston City Hospital, aerial view, UA225.004.001.00005.00027; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Boston (Mass.); Buildings; Teaching Hospitals; Parking lots; Aerial views; Slides (photographs); Boston City Hospital; South End (Boston, Mass.)
    - Tufts Lung Station, 1967; UA225.004.001.00005.00028; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Physicians; 1967; Teaching Hospitals; Pulmonary medicine; Slides (photographs); Podbielski, Joseph A.; Chodosh, Sanford; Segal, M.S.; Weiss, Earle B.; Schwartzberg, Gerald F.; Faling, L. Jack; Boston City Hospital
    - Tufts Lung Station, UA225.004.001.00005.00029; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Radiology; Physicians Buildings; Teaching Hospitals; Pulmonary medicine; Slides (photographs); Boston City Hospital
    - Boston City Hospital, Department of Inhalation Therapy, 1952-11; UA225.004.001.00005.00030; Tufts University (Box 1)
      TUSM chair named for Segal
      Boston (Mass.); Respiratory Therapy; Physicians; 1952; Teaching Hospitals; Pulmonary medicine; Slides (photographs); Segal, Maurice S.; Dulfano, M. Jack; Grossman, Doris; Mellen, Dorothy; Spigel, Robert; Cox, William; Boston City Hospital
    - Boston City Hospital, Lung Station, UA225.004.001.00005.00031; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Boston (Mass.); Physicians; Teaching Hospitals; Pulmonary medicine; Slides (photographs); Dulfano, M. Jack; Goldstein, Merrill; Boston City Hospital
    - Boston City Hospital staff with years of graduation?, UA225.004.001.00005.00032; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Probably all Tufts physicians
      Boston (Mass.); Physicians; Ink painting; Slides (photographs); Podbielski, Joseph A.; Schwartzberg, Gerald F.; Weiss, Earle B.; Faling, L. Jack; Ryder, Claire; Roberts, H.J.; Herschfus, I. Aaron; Attinger, Ernst O.; Chodosh, Sanford; Traverse, Norman; Solomon, Susan Kleeman; Schwartzberg, Gerald F.; Sabin, Stanley; Fish, Stephen; Medici, T.; Agheim, Robin; Cohen, Michael; Epstein, Ralph; Mintz, Sheldon; MacDonnell, Kenneth; Kamat, S. R.; Benkey, John F.; Salomon, Alexander; Kilgore, J.D.; Boston City Hospital
    - Boston City Hospital alumni, UA225.004.001.00005.00033; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Boston (Mass.); Physicians; Alumni and alumnae; Slides (photographs); Boston City Hospital
    - Boston City Hospital, staff of Lung Station, 1963; UA225.004.001.00005.00034; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Boston (Mass.); Physicians; Teaching Hospitals; Pulmonary medicine; Slides (photographs); Boston City Hospital
    - Boston City Hospital, Lung Station graduates, UA225.004.001.00005.00035; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Boston City Hospital, Shortell Unit, UA225.004.001.00005.00036; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Unit was named for surgeon in chief Joseph Shortell, 1946-1950.
      Boston (Mass.); Fracture fixation; Teaching Hospitals; Hospital units; Orthopedics; Slides (photographs); Boston City Hospital
    - Boston City Hospital, Shortell Unit, UA225.004.001.00005.00037; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Boston City Hospital, Shortell Unit, UA225.004.001.00005.00038; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Boston City Hospital, Shortell Unit, UA225.004.001.00005.00039; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Boston City Hospital, Shortell Unit, UA225.004.001.00005.00040; Tufts University (Box 1)
    - Boston City Hospital, Shortell Unit, 1970; UA225.004.001.00005.00041; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Boston (Mass.); Fracture fixation; Teaching Hospitals; Hospital units; Orthopedics; Traction; Slides (photographs); Boston City Hospital
    - Boston City Hospital, Shortell Unit, UA225.004.001.00005.00042; Tufts University (Box 1)
      Boston (Mass.); Teaching Hospitals; Hospital units; Slides (photographs); Boston City Hospital
    - Boston City Hospital, Shortell Unit, UA225.004.001.00005.00043; Tufts University (Box 1)